朱莉:迈克,走啦!
Julie: Mike, go!
迈克:好,是的,是的.是该快走啦.
Mike: Yep yep yep.Time to go alright.
朱莉:迈克,我是克莉丝的保姆.我可不想让你的父母进来碰到我们两个在一起亲热.
Julie: Mike, I'm Chrissy's nanny.I don't want your parents walking in on us making out.
迈克:我就是想听你说我们在一起亲热.
Mike: I just wanted to hear you say making out.
朱莉:迈克!
Julie: Mike!
迈克:好吧.哦,还有件事情……
Mike: Alright.Oh and one more thing...
朱莉:迈克!
Julie: Mike!
迈克:开个玩笑.我这就走.
Mike: Just kidding.
麦琪:啊,那么朱莉,你怎么让他睡觉的?
Maggie: Ah, so Julie, how did you make out?
朱莉:睡觉!
Julie: Make out!
麦琪:我说的是克莉丝.
Maggie: With Chrissy.
朱莉:哦对.没错.嗨,你们好.晚饭吃得怎么样?
Julie: Oh fine.Fine.Hi everybody.How was dinner?
开萝尔:很好.
Carol: Wonderful.
威利:再次感谢杰森买了单.
Wally: Thanks again Jason for picking up the check.
杰森:哦,你别提了.事实上是麦琪坚持要……你不要客气,威利.
Jason: Oh don't even mention it.Actually Maggie insist...You're welcome Wally.
麦琪:那么,朱莉,你今晚看见迈克了吗?
Maggie: So Julie, have you seen Mike tonight?
朱莉:不,没.我整晚都没看见他.这里只有我跟克莉丝.
Julie: No.I haven't seen him the whole evening.It's just been me and Chrissy.
迈克:啊,爸爸妈妈.你们是什么时候回家的?
Mike: Ah.Mum dad.When the heck did you guys get home?
奶奶,威利,你们怎么也在这?
Grandma, Wally, what are you guys doing here?
奶奶:你爸爸不让我们走,除非我们付了自己的那部分饭钱.
Grandma: Your father won't let us leave until we pay half the check.
本:好的,奶奶.
Ben: Good one grandma.
迈克:嗨,朱莉,这是苏打水,你刚才要的.
Mike: Hey Julie, here's the soda you asked for.
开萝尔:我还以为你今天整晚都没见过他呢?
Carol: I thought you hadn't seen him all evening.
麦琪:我们有条家庭重要新闻要公布.
Maggie: We have some major family news to talk about.
迈克:是吗,是什么?
Mike: Yeah, about what?
麦琪:哦就是,
Maggie: Well, a loving couple that has come a very long way in just a
有一对情人在短短的几个月里就很快发展起来了.
few short months.
迈克:啊,我认识他们吗?
Mike: Ah, do I know them?
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:对,好像是你们的奶奶,和,呃……
Jason: Yes it seems that your grandmother and, uh...
威利:威利.
Wally: Wally.
杰森:威利,已经定下结婚日期了.
Jason: Wally, have set a wedding date.
迈克:啊,好极了,奶奶!
Mike: Ah right grandma!
麦琪:对,准确地说是定在两星期后的今天.
Maggie: Yes, it's exactly two weeks from tomorrow.
奶奶:在一艘去加勒比海的游轮上.
Grandma: On a cruise to the Caribbean.
开萝尔:而且就是在那一条船上你们相识并坠入爱河的.
Carol: And on the very same boat that they met and fell in love.
奶奶:还有,你们一家都被邀请参加婚礼了.
Grandma: And, the whole family's invited.
威利:是的,是我请客.除非你们认为我会从船上掉下来.听懂了吗?从船上掉下来.
Wally: Yes.My treat.Unless you think I'm going overboard.You get it?Overboard.
麦琪:哦,朱莉,我有个想法.如果你有空的话,我们很希望你能一起来并且帮我们照顾克莉丝.
Maggie: Oh and Julie, I had an idea.If you can take the time, we'd love for you to come with us and help with Chrissy.
朱莉:一艘去加勒比海的游轮!
Julie: An ocean cruise to the Caribbean!
麦琪:呃,对.
Maggie: Uh hu.
朱莉:喔!
Julie: Wow!
麦琪:哦,还有威利,你不能帮我们和朱莉把所有的钱都给付了.
Maggie: Oh and Wally, you can't pay for all of us and Julie.
威利:不,我坚持我来付.
Wally: Oh I insist.
麦琪:我知道威利,但我认为那样的话……
Maggie: I know Wally, but I think that it's just...
杰森:麦琪,他坚持要给.下次再去游轮钱由我来付好了.
Jason: Maggie, the man insists.I'll pick up the next cruise.
本:嗨,我说你们这些人,如果我在那碰上一个漂亮女孩,你们千万不要提我抠鼻孔的事.
Ben: Hey you guys please, if I meet a pretty girl, don't mention that I pick my nose.
迈克:嗨,你这个小家伙抠鼻孔.
Mike: Hey, the little one picks his nose.
奶奶:你都已经准备好了吗,威利?
Grandma: Do you have everything Wally?
威利:哦,明天这时候我就会都准备好的.所有需要的东西都会在一个小包里.
Wally: Oh, by this time tomorrow I will.Everything I need in one little package.
麦琪:杰森,你答应了的.
Maggie: Jason, you promised.
杰森:我说过什么反对的话了吗?
Jason: Did I say anything negative?
麦琪:好,我相信在我们的讨论中你已经保证过了绝对不皱眉头,也不清嗓子和眨眼睛.
Maggie: Well I believe in our discussion, you also foresaw eyebrow lip squints, throat clears and bulging eyes.
杰森:但是麦琪……
Jason: But Maggie...
麦琪:而且也没有但是,尤其不能说但是.
Maggie: And buts.Especially big buts.
杰森:你说什么?
Jason: Pardon me?
麦琪:如果你不能给你妈妈祝福的话,起码也得给她个笑脸.
Maggie: If you can't give your mother your blessing, at least give her a silent smile.
麦琪:哦,她不太需要我的祝福,麦琪.妈妈,这趟旅行要用的东西你全都带了吗?
Maggie: Well she hardly needs my blessing Maggie.Mum, do you have everything you need for this trip?
奶奶:是的,都拿了.
Grandma: Sure do.
杰森:你看.
Jason: See.
威利:我心中充满了爱……
Wally: I'm in the mood for love...
威利和奶奶:就因为你在我身边.
Wally and Grandma: Simply because you're near me.
迈克:交流得不错.
Mike: Not a bad commute.
本:迈克,你听这个.
Ben: Mike, listen to this.
为家庭准备的有趣活动:牌局,乒乓球比赛,
Fun activities for the whole family; shuffle board,
每周二晚上的化妆舞会,哦,对我来说太无趣了!
a ping pong tournament and every Tuesday night a limbothon.
迈克,这船上应该有些我们能做的事情.
Wooooo, hold me back!Mike, there's got to be something we can do on this ship.
迈克:是的,本.肯定有的.
Mike: Yeah Bennie.There's got to be.
本:在找到之前我还是好好地休息.
Ben: And I'm not going to rest until I find it.
迈克:我也一样.
Mike: Me either.
杰森:它可能在这,麦琪.
Jason: Maybe it's out here Maggie.Women!
哦女人!一只箱子太多了,一千只又不够.
One suitcase is too many and a thousand is not enough.
朱莉:差不多了.
Julie: That was close.
迈克:不,这样就差不多了.
Mike: No, this is close.
杰森:亲爱的,我找到你的黄色提包了.你看是这个吗?
Jason: Honey, found your yellow bag.Where do you want it?
Maggie: That's not yellow, that's canary.Your shirt is yellow
杰森:我还以为它是橙色的呢.哦那这个肯定是妈妈的,
Jason: I thought it was golden.Well that must be mum's, or Wally's.
或者是威利的.妈妈,这是你浅黄色的……
Mum, is this your canary...
奶奶:我浅黄色的什么,亲爱的?
Grandma: What this about a canary dear?
杰森:提包.
Jason: Bag.
奶奶:我想那,呃,杰森对我们的做法好像有点不高兴.
Grandma: I think that uh, Jason was a little upset about what we were doing.
威利:我们做了什么?
Wally: What were we doing?
奶奶:我们在一起亲热.
Grandma: Making out.
威利:我知道.我就喜欢听你说我们在一起亲热.
Wally: I know.I just wanted to hear you say making out.
(船开了)
(Boat leaving)
迈克:爸爸.
Mike: Dad.
杰森:嗨迈克.
Jason: Hey Mike.
迈克:嗨,我们是在向谁挥手?
Mike: Hey who are we waving to?
杰森:我不知道迈克.我就是随着大家一起挥手.
Jason: I don't know Mike.Just go with the flow.
本:儿童乐园.等我有了小孩我会再来的.赌场,不错,不错,不错.
Ben: Children's play room.When I have kids I'll be back.Casino.Well, well, well.
女士:我最后说一遍,你还太小了.现在给我快走!
Lady: For the last time, you are too young.Now stay out!
本:你把我赶走的唯一原因就是因为我一直在赢.这些人,等我足够大了就会有其它事情做了.化妆舞会,狂饮啤酒……?
Ben: And the only reason you are throwing me out is because I was winning
Man, there's got o be something I'm old enough to do.Limbothon, beer drinking
多琳:小伙子.您要顶小船长的帽子吗?
Doreen: Young man.Would you like a little captain's hat?
本:好吧.
Ben: That's ok.
多琳:它们是免费的.
Doreen: They are free.
本:给我爸爸也来一顶吧.
Ben: My dad will probably want one.
多琳:我叫多琳.这个船上专门照顾小孩的.你叫什么名字?
Doreen: I'm Doreen.Your ships kids' officer.What's your name?
本:本希弗.
Ben: Ben Seaver.
多琳:希弗.希弗,希弗,希弗.
Doreen: Seaver.Seaver, Seaver, Seaver.
本:可能是威利欧彭迈.
Ben: It might be under Wally Openmyer.
多琳:欧彭迈的婚礼?我刚碰见过他们.
Doreen: The Openmyer wedding party?I just met them.
他们真是相配.
They are such a cute couple.I'm taking care of all the bridal arrangements.
我负责婚礼的一切事务.我还是"你这艘船上的社交顾问".
I'm also "your ships social director".
嗨,
Hey, let me show you are darned exciting play room.
我带你去看看游乐室.你想和你妈妈一起来吗?
You want a make up holder for your mum?
本:哦,不用.
Ben: Oh that's ok.
女士:(说瑞典语)
Bikini Lady: (speaks in Swedish)
多琳:我也是"你这艘船上的语言翻译".
Doreen: I'm also "your ships linguist".
她们是斯德哥尔摩大学体操队的.
This is the University of Stockholm's gymnastic team.
本:喔.
Ben: Wow.
女士:(一些瑞典语)
Bikini Lady: (more Swedish)
多琳:(用瑞典语回答)
Doreen: (reply in Swedish)
本:你刚才说什么?你刚才说了些什么?
Ben: What did she just say?What did she just say?
多琳:我要带她们去游泳池.
Doreen: I'll have to show them to the pool.
本:我来吧,我是这艘船上的向导.
Ben: I'll do it.I'm your ships hornball.
奶奶:那天威利找不到吃饭的座位,而我这正好有个空位.
Grandma: So Wally had no place to eat,
接下来的就都是些历史了.
but I just happened to have an empty seat.And the rest is history.
麦琪:这里就是他向你求婚的地方?
Maggie: And is this where you proposed?
威利:不是的.那是在厄玛的屋子里,她家的阳台上.
Wally: Nah.That was in Urma's cabin, on the balcony.
奶奶:在一轮满月下.
Grandma: Under a full moon.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:哦!
Jason: Oh!
本:我错过午饭了吗?
Ben: Did I miss lunch?
麦琪:是的,本.本!你怎么湿透了?
Maggie: Yes Ben.Ben!You are all wet.
本:我也不知道怎么回事.
Ben: Tell me about it.
杰森:哦,快去换件干的衣服.
Jason: Well go change into some dry clothes.
本:没关系.我想我正在学游泳的劲头上.
Ben: That's alright.I think I'll just try swimming in my trunks for a change.
威利:你们几个以前都没坐过游船吗?
Wally: Neither of you's ever been on a cruise before?
杰森:啊……
Jason: Ah...
麦琪:没.
Maggie: No.
开萝尔:奶奶,妈妈,不用一小时告别单身生活舞会就要开始了,你们千万不要迟到了.我说完了,再见!
Carol: Grandma, mum, the bachelorette party's in less than an hour and you don't want to be late.That's all I'm saying.
奶奶:哦,开萝尔真的是个好女孩.
Grandma: Oh Carol's such a good girl.
麦琪:我在想她有什么计划.
Maggie: I wonder what she's got planned.
奶奶:哦没有什么.
Grandma: Oh I wonder.
杰森:啊妈妈……
Jason: Ah mum...
奶奶:是的,亲爱的.
Grandma: Yes dear.
杰森:我有一样小东西要送给你.
Jason: I have a little something for you.
奶奶:一样结婚礼物?
Grandma: A wedding gift?
杰森:没有礼物那么隆重,只是为了你的婚礼而准备的一些东西.
Jason: It's not a gift so much, but yes it is for the wedding.
威利:啊!
Wally: Ahh!
杰森:我们会和你在一起的.你能给我们几分钟吗?
Jason: We'll be right with you.Can you give us just one minute?
奶奶:哦,杰森,什么事情?
Grandma: Well Jason, what is it?
杰森:哦,妈妈,
Jason: Well mum, you know, uh, marriage is a wonderful beautiful thing.
你知道,呃,结婚是一件奇妙而美好的事.
And the opposite of marriage, divorce, that's a horrible ugly thing mum.
但作为结婚的反面,离婚,
And god forbid it should ever happen to you and Wally after you get married,
是一件很可怕的丑陋的事情,妈妈.
but, uh, well just,
上帝希望你和威利结婚后再离婚那样的事情永远不会发生,但是,呃,
I would like you to have the piece of mind that something like this would
只是,我希望你有足够的心理准备会发生如同这上面写着的那种事.
provide.
奶奶:是什么?
Grandma: What's this?
杰森:只是我的律师写的一些东西.
Jason: Just a little something I had my lawyer whip up.
真的很简单.
It's really very simple.
奶奶:标准婚前协议.
Grandma: Standard pre-nuptial agreement.
杰森:对对对.呃,我想当你看到它时第一反应肯定会反感,妈妈,以后你会觉得这很明智……呃……
Jason: Yep yep yep.It's uh, I think as soon as you get over your
initial reaction, mum you are going to see the wisdom.....uh
威利:怎么了?
Wally: What's the matter?
奶奶:威利,我想要呼吸新鲜空气.
Grandma: Wally, I think I need some air.
威利:发生什么事了?他说了些什么?
Wally: What went on?What did he say?
杰森:那么,呃,在婚礼仪式上再见吧.什么?整个午餐时间我还不够礼貌吗?
Jason: So uh, see you two kids at rehearsal.What?Wasn't I polite all through lunch?
迈克:那么,
Mike: So, what do you say,
今晚我们单独乘小船一起去玩好吗?
you and me both have our own private little lifeboat girl tonight?
朱莉:迈克,我不能.开萝尔邀请我一起去参加单身女孩舞会.我得去.
Julie: Mike I can't.They all invited me to the bachelorette party.I have to go.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
朱莉:因为我是个单身女孩.我7点钟以后就完全无事可做了.
Julie: Cos I'm a bachelorette.Who's totally free after seven o'clock?
迈克:哦,真是太巧了.我是个单身汉,7点以后也完全无事可做了.
Mike: Oh what a coinky dink.I'm a bachelor who's totally free after seven o'clock.
男人:哦,看到刚结婚的夫妇和小孩子在一起感觉总是很好.
Man: Oh, it's always nice to see a young married couple with a baby.
迈克:哦,我们还没结婚.嗨,不介意我来推车吧?嗨,看克莉丝多高兴.
Mike: Oh, we're not married.Hey, mind if I drive?Hey, hold on Chrissy.
朱莉:迈克,我感觉现在和你走得很近.
Julie: I feel very close to you right now Mike.
迈克:我们俩是很近.
Mike: Hey we are.
朱莉:我是说认真的,我已经爱上你了.
Julie: I'm serious.I'm falling in love with you.
迈克:来吧.水正好.
Mike: Well come on in.The water's fine.
女士:哦,多快乐的一对年轻夫妇啊.
Lady: Oh, a nice young married couple.
朱莉:我们是……谢谢.这样回答方便多了.
Julie: We're...thank you.It's easier.
本:迈克,你在哪呢?
Ben: Mike, where are you?
朱莉:我7点钟和你在这里见面.
Julie: I'll meet you right back here at seven.
迈克:7点．好的,别迟到了.
Mike: Seven o'clock.Ok, don't be late.
本:迈克!你在哪呢?
Ben: Mike!Where are you?
迈克:我就在这儿.
Mike: I'm right here.
本:迈克,这简直太酷了.迈克,迈克,迈克,迈克,
Ben: Mike, this is so cool.Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike.
迈克,迈克,迈克,迈克,迈克,你肯定不会相信的.今天是我们的幸运日.
Mike, Mike, Mike, you will not believe this.Today is our lucky day.
迈克:什么?是什么?
Mike: What?What is it?
本:迈克,在这艘船上有20个世界上最辣的女孩子.
Ben: Mike, there are twenty of the hottest babes in the world on this boat.
迈克:怎么了.
Mike: So.
本:我是说20个瑞典女孩,金发,体操队的.
Ben: We are talking Swedish, blonde, gymnast.
迈克:嗨,本,女孩子除了长相外还得具备些别的东西.
Mike: Hey Ben, look, there is much more to a woman than the way she looks.
我是说你得考虑很多其它事情比如,个性,智商,
I mean you've got to take into account all kinds of things like,
还要呃,还要她们的呃,
a personality and her intelligence, and uh, and her uh, uh, uh.
呃,呃.我在说些什么?
So what was I saying?
本:谁在说些什么?
Ben: What was who saying?
麦琪:杰森,
Maggie: Jason, I have an idea.
我不知道你为什么会在你妈妈的婚礼上扔这么一个炸弹?
Why don't you just stink bomb you're mother's bachelorette party?
杰森:算了麦琪!婚前协议又不是没听说过.
Jason: Come on Maggie!Pre-nuptial agreements are hardly un heard of.
麦琪:我可绝不会把这叫做一件浪漫的结婚礼物.
Maggie: Well I wouldn't exactly call it a romantic gift.
杰森:哦,有时候浪漫是不可能维持永久的.
Jason: Well sometimes romance doesn't last for ever.
麦琪:杰森,别跟我来这一套.
Maggie: Jason, don't give me straight lines like that.
杰森:你能因为我身为一个儿子为自己母亲的利益着想而责怪我吗?
Jason: Can you blame me a man for trying to look out for his mother's best interest?
麦琪:是的,你能.
Maggie: Yes, I can.
克莉丝如果你想方便,现在正是时候.
Chrissy if you are ever going to have gas, now is the time.
奶奶:我想杰森应该更懂事点.
Grandma: You would think Jason would know better.
麦琪:他在想些什么?
Maggie: What was he thinking?
奶奶:真是个笨蛋.
Grandma: What a boob.
麦琪:厄玛,那个笨蛋也是我的丈夫.
Maggie: Urma, that boob is my husband.
奶奶:对不起.
Grandma: Sorry.
开萝尔:你的单身女孩舞会就快开始了.请再给我10秒钟的时间.
Carol: Your bachelorette party is almost ready.Just give me ten seconds.
奶奶:好的,好的,好的.
Grandma: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
开萝尔:奶奶发生什么事了?
Carol: What's with grandma?
麦琪:哦,你爸爸刚刚做了件傻事.
Maggie: Oh your dad did something stupid.
开萝尔:他在想些什么?
Carol: What was he thinking?
麦琪:真是个笨蛋.
Maggie: What a boob.
开萝尔:妈妈,这个笨蛋也是我的爸爸.
Carol: Mum, that boob is my father.
麦琪:对不起.你知道吗,
Maggie: Sorry.You know Urma, no matter what Jason does,
厄玛?不管杰森做了什么,不管这件事情有多傻,
no matter how silly or twisted or border line nut bar,
多可笑,他完全是因为爱你才那样做的.
he does it out of love for you.
奶奶:你说的对,麦琪.
Grandma: You're right Maggie.
麦琪:你不能让这件事情坏了你整个星期的心情.
Maggie: And you can't let him spoil this week for you.
奶奶:说得对.
Grandma: True.
麦琪:快,走吧.
Maggie: Come on.
开萝尔:欢迎.我们都在等着你们呢.
Carol: Welcome aboard.We've been expecting you.
麦琪和厄玛:哦,孩子们!
Maggie and Urma: Oh kids!
开萝尔:厄玛希弗,跟你的单身日子吻别吧.唱起来,跳起来,享受舞会吧,请你们欣赏惊人的洛伦佐.
Carol: Urma Seaver, kiss your single days goodbye.Have a punch, have a cracker and have a ball, as you watch the amazing Lorenzo!
歌曲和洛伦佐乐器:开动你的马力.朝着高速公路.
Song and Lorenzo strips: Get your motor running.Heading on the high way.
麦琪:呃,呃,呃,呃.我不行.开萝尔,这是什么?
Maggie: Uh, uh, uh, uh.I can't.Carol, what is this?
开萝尔:没事的,妈妈.他是个专家.
Carol: It's ok mum.He's a professional.
麦琪:你在哪里找到他的?
Maggie: Where did you find him?
开萝尔:他是赌场的一个交易员.
Carol: Well he's the dealer at the casino.
麦琪:我想你要到21岁才能进赌场.
Maggie: I thought you had to be twenty one to get into the casino.
开萝尔:我不是在赌场碰见他的.我和他是在桑拿浴室碰到的.
Carol: I didn't meet him at the casino.I met him at the sauna.
麦琪:开萝尔,你父亲的妈妈在这儿.这种表演不太适合.
Maggie: Carol, this is your fathers' mother here.This is not appropriate entertainment.
奶奶:没关系.等他表演一结束我们就让他离开.
Grandma: That's right.We'll tell him to leave as soon as he's finished.
(瑞典女孩在游泳池尖叫)
(Swedish ladies screaming in pool)
迈克:这里有20个瑞典妞,但是我却什么也不能做.
Mike: Twenty Swedish girls, and I can't do a thing about it.
本:嗨,迈克.你在上面干什么?到下面来.水很暖和.而且这里不只是有水.
Ben: Hey Mike.What you doing up there?Come on in.The waters warm.And not just the water.
迈克:嗨,不谢谢本.
Mike: Hey, no thanks Bennie.
我还是在这儿站着看看.
I'd rather stay up here and watch.(Under his breath) From a safe distance.
保持距离.来吧!
Carry on..
迈克脑子里在想:哦,不,不,不.哦,偏偏这个时候.
Mike in his mind: Oh, no, no, no.Oh.Ooh
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why now?
本:嗨,迈克,扔过来.
Ben: Hey Mike, give it here.
(尖叫)
Swedish girls: (screaming)
本:迈克,快来.我们还缺一个人.
Ben: Mike come on.One more person is needed.
迈克:不,听着.我7点约了个人.
Mike: No listen.I've got to meet someone at seven o'clock.
瑞典女孩:来吧,来吧,来吧.
Swedish girls: Please.Please.Please.
迈克:好吧,嗨.如果这是为了促进国际关系缓和世界紧张气氛,就玩五分钟怎么样?(跳进水里)现在分成3个组了.
Mike: Well, hey.If it will improve international relations and ease world tensions, what's five minutes?(Jumps in water) That's three aside for chunky wunky.
(朱莉在等迈克)
(Julie waiting for Mike)
多琳:我想"演员艾维斯在船上的表演"是你们的婚礼节目之一?
Doreen: I understand "your ships Elvis impersonator" is part of the wedding?
艾维斯:是的.
Elvis: Yo.
奶奶:我知道这看起来有点奇怪,
Grandma: I know it seems odd,
但是在我们相见的那个神奇的晚上艾维斯也在.
but he was part of the magical night when we met.
所以在我们举行婚礼时不能没有这位王子.
And we just couldn't tie the knot without the prince.
威利:国王.
Wally: The King.
多琳:那么,现在请大家注意!
Doreen: Now then, pay attention!
这是过道,这些是椅子,这是一个很不高兴的人.
This is the aisle, and these are the chairs, and this is a very unhappy man.
杰森:不,我没有不高兴.
Jason: No, I'm not unhappy.I was just thinking of a way I might apologize.
我只是在想个表示道歉的方式.我的婚前协议令大家都不高兴,
I got everybody so upset with that whole prenuptial thing,
希望你们能忘记我把它带来的事,好吗?
and please just forget I ever brought it up.Ok?
麦琪:哦杰森,真是太好了.
Maggie: Oh Jason, that's so nice.
奶奶:谢谢你杰森.
Grandma: Thank you Jason.
多琳:他真是个可爱的宝贝.
Doreen: Isn't he a sweet heart.
艾维斯:是的.
Elvis: Yo.
杰森:嗨.
Jason: Hey.
威利:杰森……
Wally: Jason...
杰森:威利.
Jason: Wally.
开萝尔:从明天起我们就该叫他威利爷爷了.
Carol: It's going to be Grandpa Wally after tomorrow.
杰森:威利爷爷!
Jason: Grandpa Wally!Now the last thing I want to do is upset anybody.
现在我想做的最后一件事是让大家不高兴的事.
Really.I just wanted to make sure nobody has any lingering suspicions
我只是想确认确实没有人在一直怀疑威利完全是冲着钱和这位感情脆弱容易冲动的女人结婚的.最好没人.
that Wally might be some kind of gold digger on a pension dragging in
让我们随便玩吧.
an emotionally vulnerable woman.Nough said.Let's have some fun.
麦琪:一直怀疑?
Maggie: Lingering suspicions!
威利:完全是冲着钱!
Wally: Gold digger on a pension!
奶奶:一个感情易冲动的女人!
Grandma: An emotionally vulnerable woman!
开萝尔:最好没人!
Carol: Nough said!
杰森:好吧,可能我要为我刚才的道歉道歉了.
Jason: Well ok, maybe I should apologize for my apology now.
麦琪:不,不要再说任何字了.
Maggie: No, no don't say anything.
威利:就一分钟……
Wally: Now just a minute here...
奶奶:威利,威利.算了,忘了这事.请你,为了我,谢谢你.
Grandma: Wally, Wally.Forget it.Please, for me.Thank you.
多琳:他这样还算是个可爱的宝贝吗?
Doreen: Isn't he a sweet heart?
艾维斯:是的.
Elvis: Yo!
(朱莉还在等)
(Julie still waiting)
(迈克和本在接受瑞典女孩的按摩)
(Mike and Ben getting massages from the Swedish girls)
迈克:往下,再往下.
Mike: Lower, lower.Ah!
啊!
You know Ben, I just realized that this is the first time in my life I've
本,我突然想到这是我有生以来第一次同时被八只女人的手在我身上摸.
been touched by eight female hands at the same time.
本:对我来说是第二次了.
Ben: Second for me.
迈克:对了,说的对.你是说那晚四个女孩一起给你换尿布?喂,是谁呀……
Mike: Yeah right.When did four girls put sun tan lotion on you at night?Well hello...
朱莉:朱莉.
Julie: Julie.
迈克:朱莉,真有趣我……朱莉!朱莉你看,不是你想的那样.好吧,哈哈.嗨朱莉.本,本,看这是谁.她是朱莉.
Mike: Julie, that's funny I...Julie!Julie look, its not what it looks like.Alright, ha ha.Hey Julie.Bennie, Bennie.Look who it is.It's Julie.
瑞典女孩:嗨朱莉.
Swedish Girls: Hi Julie.
朱莉:这是怎么回事?
Julie: What is it then?
迈克:哦,我是在帮几个外国人解决她们在美国的前几个困难的日子.
Mike: Well uh, I was just helping some foreigners with their first difficult days in America.
朱莉:我们是在公海上.
Julie: We're in international waters.
迈克:对了.如果我一小时前早知道这点,我就不会来了.
Mike: Yeah.Well if I found that out an hour ago, I wouldn't have been here.
朱莉:你想让我相信你让我等了那么长时间不是因为在和其他姑娘调情?
Julie: You expect me to believe that you didn't stand me up to get greased
down by a million other women?
瑞典女孩:迈克,还没好吗?
Swedish girl: Mikey, you do me now ya?
朱莉:我信错你了.
Julie: I trusted you.
迈克:呃听着.你们自己先玩好吗?
Mike: Uh listen.You'll have to start without me alright.
朱莉:哦,我想我得先走了.
Julie: Well maybe I should too.
迈克:请你小声点.
Mike: Would you keep it down.
朱莉:小声点?
Julie: Keep it down.
迈克:是的.你看,本就在那儿.你知道,我们的关系.
Mike: Yes come on.Ben is right over there.You know.Our relationship.
朱莉:什么关系?
Julie: What relationship.
迈克:嗨朱莉.朱莉!
Mike: Hey Julie.Julie!
多琳:然后"我们的船长"就会站在这里说:"如果在场的所有人中有谁知道这对夫妇有什么不能结合的原因,
Doreen: And then "your ships captain" will stand here and say: "If anyone
请现在就说出来,
among us knows why this couple should not be joined in holy matrimony,
否则就请永远保持沉默.
speak now or forever hold your peace".
杰森:哈哈哈.刚才我完全在想其他事情.你继续吧.
Jason: Ha ha ha.I was thinking of something else totally.Please.
威利:嗨朋友.你那一套我受够了.
Wally: Look pal.I've had just about enough of your hooee.
奶奶:威利!
Grandma: Wally!
威利:哦厄玛,我不能再忍了.
Wally: Well Urma, I can't take this.
奶奶:听着.不管杰森怎么说怎么做,都完全是发自他的爱.
Grandma: Look.No matter what Jason says or does, he's doing it out of love.
威利:这和你的傻瓜儿子无关.
Wally: This isn't about your son the boob.
这是你和我的生活.
This is about you and me and our life together.
现在让我们忘掉你的傻瓜一家庭!
Now it's time we forgot your goofy family.
全家人:什么?
Family: What?
奶奶:起码我的傻瓜一家还懂得礼节来参加婚礼.
Grandma: Well at least my goofy family had the courtesy to show up.
威利:哦,那算是件好事吗?
Wally: Oh and that's a good thing?
奶奶:你不要用那种语气跟我说话.
Grandma: Don't you talk to me in that tone.
杰森:我们先停一停我们的对话吧,再重新排练一遍怎么样?
Jason: Can we just table this conversation and get on with the rehearsal?
威利:住嘴!
Wally: Shut up!
你不能对我的儿子说让他住嘴.
Grandma: Don't you tell my son to shut up.
麦琪:呃呃,厄玛,威利,你们先冷静下来.我们好像忘了我们来这是干什么的.多琳,你为什么不……
Maggie: Uh uh, Urma, Wally, why don't you just calm down.We are losing sight of hwy we are here.Doreen, why don't you just...
多琳:"我们的船长"会让你们向前一步然后表示你们将终生在一起.
Doreen: And then "your ships captain" will ask you two to step forward
and take each other for life.
奶奶:终生?
Grandma: For life!
威利:你这口气说得好像听到了被判死刑一样.
Wally: Well you make it sound like an alternative to the death penalty.
奶奶:或许你希望来个大赦.
Grandma: Well maybe you would like a pardon.
威利:或许我想要个直升飞机.
Wally: Well maybe I would like a helicopter.
奶奶:哦,你不用等直升飞机了.游泳吧!
Grandma: Well don't wait for the helicopter.Swim for it!
杰森:这就是我那份婚前协议想要预防的那种会出现的难以预料的情况.
Jason: This is exactly the kind of unforeseen situation prenuptial agreements
are designed to protect you against.
麦琪:哈!多琳:各位亲爱的乘客请注意.
Maggie: Ha! Doreen: Attention happy passengers.
希望大家在船上的第一天过得都好.也许你找到了什么特别的人现在正和他们在一起.
I hope you all enjoyed the first day of your dream cruise.
也许你计划和你那位特别的人一起前来.总而言之,
Maybe you found a special person and you are with them right now.
我能感受到.
Or maybe you planned ahead and brought that special person with you.
今夜的气氛是浪漫的.请大家记住,
Either way, I can just feel it.Romance is in the air tonight.
我们还有六天的美好时光要一起度过,请尽情享受!
And remember everybody, there are six more wonderful days where this came
00:21:03,500
from.Enjoy!